♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
It's that time of year again.
Are you a New England dirtbag
who wants to run with bulls,
but thinks Spain is gay?
Then don't miss
the Seriously Wicked Bull Run
in South Attleboro, Mass!
You and your friends can run
from a bunch live bulls,
and lots of times, there's a
chick whose boob comes out.
Order your tickets
before it too late!
Toilets limited.
Wow, that seems
pretty cool.
Nah, I don't know.
Seems pretty lame to me.
Yeah, waste of time.
I agree.
Hey Joe,
isn't this your round?
Sure.
I'll wheel over to the bar
and bring back your beers
one by one in my lap.
You guys, we are
so doing that bull run.
Buying the tickets as we speak!
But we can't tell Joe.
Of course not,
he'll  be dead weight.
You can't do a bull run
with a guy in a wheelchair.
Yeah, this is for athletes.
Just the regular wash, please.
And, uh, I'm supposed to mention
that I saw you on LivingSocial?
Was that worth it?
Was that worth the
one dollar you saved?
I'm sorry, we're not doing
that promotion anymore.
Oh-ho!
All the humiliation,
none of the reward.
You know, some people are okay
with the drive-through car wash.
Me, I'm a fan of the hand job.
Hi, I'm Brian.
Yes, I like to have fun
with language.
You're so funny.
I'm Tori.
I got hit by a car
in high school,
so I don't have to work.
Cool. Hey, so what's
your afternoon like?
I don't have plans.
Maybe we could grab lunch
and then see what happens.
This will not end well.
Like eating an artichoke.
Good Lord!
I ate nothing and I'm
soaking wet for some reason.
So, you guys all pumped
to run with the bulls?
You bet, this is gonna be
my first exercise
since I chased that balloon.
Hey, what's going on?
Hey, Joe.
We are competing...
in the international Chef
Boyardee look-alike contest.
Oh, well,
where's your chef hat?
You guys are gonna lose.
Especially Cleveland.
He's in the Cream of Wheat
competition,
which is down the street.
We-we got to go now.
We're very late.
Well, this is funny, because...
guess where I'm going.
And I got the hat.
You guys are dead!
Look, Joe.
We didn't want to tell
you, but we're going
to the Seriously
Wicked Bull Run.
We didn't invite you because we
didn't think you could keep up.
Yeah, we thought it seemed
too dangerous for, uh,
incapacitated, half-man,
shrivel-legged gimps.
And we didn't want
to hurt your feelings.
Come on, my handicap
has never held me back.
I'm coming with you guys.
Joe, you peed in your bag
while you said that.
Can you honestly say
that you didn't pee
just now while you
were talking?
Okay, you can come.
Wow, that was amazing.
Hey, uh, uh,
just to be clear,
I don't really
think you're a whore.
I-I just need to say that
to, you know, to finish.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
yeah, of course.
And obviously, I don't think
you're my Uncle Dale.
Good, good, same page.
Oh, crap,
my husband's home early.
Wait a minute,
you're married?!
And he's here?
Now?!
Yeah, that's him.
You've got to get out of here.
He's really jealous.
I think he's bitter
because he never got
the credit he deserved
for killing Osama bin Laden.
Your husband's a Navy SEAL?!
What the hell
is going on here?!
What is this?
Ruff!
You got a dog?
Uh... yeah!
I rescued him
from the pound.
Well, hey there, buddy.
Wow, his nose is super wet!
He must be healthy.
Uh, and somebody's been
rooting in a sardine can.
Well, I'm gonna
grab a shower.
Great, honey.
Oh. Oh, my God,
that was close.
Yeah, but think about it.
As long as he thinks
you're our new pet,
we can keep fooling
around behind his back.
Huh, you're right.
Wow, this could be
an even better scam
than that claw machine
at the arcade.
Damn it, this game is so stupid!
It's impossible to do anything
with a dumb, crappy claw!
Hey, that's mean,
and it's not even true!
I'm leaving!
Dang it!
You need a little help?
No!
If you could angle up the ring,
then I could kind of hook it.
How do you drive?
Bad!
We clearly overdressed.
They have the type
of fat white woman here
that not even
I am interested in.
Ladies, gentlemen,
and alternative high school
graduates,
get ready to run for your lives!
Aah! I shouldn't
have worn high heels!
Oh, stop it!
You look great.
Oh, well, I didn't
want all this attention.
Cleveland, why do you let them
talk you into these things?
This is how
people pleasers die!
Hey, guys, after this,
let's beat alligators
with sticks or something.
You read my mind!
We just talked about this!
This is amazing!
I told you guys I could do it!
Look... out...
Joe...!
Joe, oh, my God!
Are you all right?!
I can't feel anything
below my neck!
I can't move a muscle, guys!
Oh, my God!
Joe's completely
paralyzed!
Oop, that's me.
That's unfortunate.
That's Lois, hold on.
Hey, babe.
Uh, good.
Little hiccup, but fun.
You guys!
I've been trying to keep
my birthday a secret.
No, Dr. Hartman, we're not
here for your birthday.
We're here for Joe.
Don't sugarcoat it, Doc.
Just give it to me straight.
Well, Mr. Swanson, I did
an exploratory procedure,
which revealed extensive damage.
Please, just tell me--
am I completely paralyzed?
I'm afraid...
of ghosts.
And yes.
Mr. Swanson
has lost all movement,
and will require
around-the-clock care.
Most of it disgusting.
Oh, my God, Bonnie,
I'm so sorry.
If there's anything
I can do...
There actually is.
Could you collect
my mail forever?
I'm leaving Joe
and moving to Europe.
I didn't sign up for this.
Bonnie, wait!
God, this is awful.
What am I gonna do?
Well, seems like you folks
have this all taken care of.
Surprise!
Oh, you guys!
Hey, don't go in
that room back there.
It's, like,
super sad.
Coming up, quintuplets
born at Quahog General.
What?
That's...
Oh, that's supposed
to be "burn"?
Oh, coming up, quintuplets
burn at Quahog General.
Hey, honey, get in here.
Check this out--
the way he's sitting,
it looks like the dog's
watching the news.
You like watching the
news, you dumb dog?
Well, I'm off to do what
former Navy SEALs do--
sell lawnmowers.
Wow, he really
has no idea.
Hey, want to take
a shower with me?
Sure.
Man, this is a pretty sweet gig.
Like being a member
of Daft Punk.
Look at this old Casio keyboard
from the 1980s
that I have found.
Watch what happens
when I push this demo button.
♪ ♪
Hello, Daft Punk?
Great song.
Here's a Grammy.
Oh-ho-ho!
You know, is funny.
Until you spoke, I did
not know we were French!
There you go, Joe.
All settled.
Now, which wall
would you like to look at
for the rest of your life?
I don't know,
maybe that one.
I-I have no idea
what you're pointing at, Joe.
You got to meet us halfway.
Look, guys, I don't want
to be a burden to anyone.
You go ahead
and live your lives.
I'll be fine.
We can't just
leave you, Joe.
So before we go, I'm gonna
put the remote in your mouth.
Here's a can of chili.
And the opener we'll put...
in your mouth.
And here's a magazine I thought
you might like to read.
I'm gonna put it
in your mouth.
You're a good friend, Peter.
Joe, I just wish
we could do more,
but obviously your
mouth is full.
And you probably don't want
any reminders of Bonnie
around the house, so I cleared
out all of her underwear.
Okay, don't be a stranger.
Yeah, 'cause we're not
supposed to talk to those.
I don't know, I'm not sure
I feel right about leaving Joe.
Doesn't seem like he's gonna be
able to take care of himself.
Yeah, we're-we're kind
of all he has now.
What-- Joe?
What're you talking about?
He's fine.
Look, he's already watching
The Price Is Right in there.
Oop, he's biting
too hard on the volume.
Okay, you can play over there
in the sandbox, honey.
Mommy's just gonna
read her book.
Okay, I'm just gonna
walk 30 feet away,
and then panic
because I can't see you.
Can you fit me in
at 10:00 tomorrow?
It's getting a little
long on the sides.
Brian? What are you
doing on a leash?
And who's that?
Be cool.
This is the guy whose
wife I'm banging.
Oh, what a romantic way
to put it.
Yeah, it's great.
I just pretend
to be their dog,
and then when he
leaves for work,
I get to go to the pound,
if you know what I mean.
God, Brian,
you are such a scumbag.
I can't believe you--
Mommy! Mommy!
Where's my Mommy?!
I have no one and nothing!
I'm right here, honey.
Oh, thank God.
She's such a gross hog.
Joe, you can't
just sit here.
You need intellectual
stimulation.
So I brought something
to read to you.
It's the word search
from the Sunday Circular.
"Kangaroo."
Let's see if we
can find that one.
"Outback."
I think it's an
Australian theme.
"Koala."
It definitely is.
Can't make out this one.
"Abor... Aborgine...
Aborgina"?
That's what they call
eggplant down there.
You know what?
Forget this.
I'll just read
to you from Jet.
Look, this whole page is
all the Wayans brothers
sitting in different
positions.
How you suppose they come up
with all them positions?
You could give me
a million years.
I just ain't
wired that way.
Marlon's like
a rubber man.
He can sit in
any kind of way.
Here's Keenan telling the
younger ones how to sit.
Like they
gonna listen.
Damon's doing
his own thing.
No surprise there.
That's Damon.
You enjoying
all this, Joe?
I'm honestly
just glad it seems
like you have
something you like.
Hey, my laptop's
out of battery.
You want to have sex?
Sure, I've almost finished
my sandwich, anyway.
Oh, come on, I don't want
to have to watch this.
Yeah, that's right.
I was the only one
who didn't get to meet Biden.
You know what?
Screw this.
I'm out of here.
Ha! Skewered.
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
You're my dog.
You're not going anywhere.
Besides, I need you, boy.
Now more than ever.
I think my wife
is cheating on me.
Hey, Tori, it's Brian.
I'm getting
the Chinese food for us.
I think I'm gonna order
some Me Like Bang Ho.
That's-that's not a real thing,
I'm talking about sex.
All right,
I'll be there in five.
Man, when I find
that son of a bitch,
I'm gonna rip
his head off.
God, what a nightmare.
That guy's even scarier
than a thesaurus-asaurus.
Tread, stomp, trudge.
Growl, roar, ululate.
Antonym-- whisper.
What's wrong with him?
He's on the spectrum.
"Spectrum"?
In my day we'd
throw him in the army
and have him
play the bugle.
Peter, this just isn't working.
We can't take
proper care of Joe.
It's a huge amount of work
and we don't have
any idea what we're doing.
Quagmire's right.
It's too much.
I just think he'd
be better off
under the care of grumpy,
Filipino nurses.
Yeah, that's why
I looked into it,
and we've reserved
a place for him
at the State Home for
Mentals and Bastards.
Oh, my God, sometimes
they whip them with hoses...
outside?!
This is perfect!
Hi, I work here.
I don't think
this guy works here.
Hi, can I help you?
Yeah, this is Joe Swanson.
We arranged for a 9:15 dump-off?
Go on, guys, get out of here.
I'll be fine.
Bye, Joe.
Take care, man.
See ya, Joe.
Hold on, guys.
There's one last thing
I got to say to my friend.
Hey, Joe, you know
that movie you told me to watch
that you said was
your favorite movie of all time,
and you said
I had to watch it?
Backdraft-- you
finally watched it?
Yeah.
Wasn't it great?
I thought it was stupid.
Take care, Joe.
You know, tha-that state home we
left Joe in didn't seem so bad.
Yeah, it's got
to be good.
I mean, Napoleon Bonaparte
was there.
Would the French people
let their boss walk around
in stained underwear
trying to stab people
if the place wasn't nice?
Yeah, no, no,
y-you're right, you're right.
Joe will get
much better care there.
I still feel bad.
Come on, you guys.
Joe's gonna be fine.
He'll fit in great there.
Not like when
I went to Hogwarts.
Slytherin.
Hufflepuff.
Housing for registered
sex offenders!
Aw.
Oh, Tori, thank God.
Listen, you got
to unchain me.
Look what Vic did.
Tell me about it.
He's lost his mind.
That's why I'm gonna go stay
with my mother in Baltimore
and work at her wife's bar.
Wait, what?!
Tori, come back!
Damn it!
Wow, shocker.
Your gross hookup
from the car wash ended poorly?
Stewie, thank God!
How'd you find me?
Well, you remember
when the vet knocked you out
to take out that rotten tooth?
He also put a tracking chip
in your neck.
What?! That's a total
violation of my rights!
Heh, I like how you're
chained up in a yard
and still trying
to pretend you're a guy.
Look, you got to help me.
Her husband's a maniac and the
only reason he hasn't killed me
is because he thinks
I'm just his pet dog.
Hmm, he's got
a padlock on here.
But don't worry,
I'll figure something out.
Well, hurry, 'cause I'm trapped
like a baseball announcer.
And the count is two and two.
Garcia steps
off the mound again,
virtually guaranteeing
that my wife
will be asleep when I get home.
The big right-hander kicks
a little dirt and tosses
the rosin bag as my children
grow up without me.
Okay, and now a fan in the
stands is giving me the finger.
I agree.
Hey, I don't know
if you can hear it,
but I'm peeing
in my coffee cup right now.
There you are.
Where the hell have you been?
I got arrested for huckin'
a TV/VCR combo off the dam.
Off the damn what?
Off the damn overpass.
Oh...
God, I love you, Lois.
That was like great sex.
But seriously,
it-it was bad.
It hit a school bus.
Oh, my God!
Well-well, can you
go talk to Joe?
Maybe he can put in a word for
you down at the police station.
Yeah, yeah, Joe, yeah, may--
yeah, maybe, maybe.
Do you, uh, you-you
want a back rub?
Peter, what's going on?
Uh, what do you mean?
Whenever you offer
me a back rub,
it means you're
hiding something.
You, uh, you-you
want a back rub?
We may or may not
have put Joe
in a smelly home
for the goofy.
What?! Peter, those places
are a horror show!
Joe's your friend!
How could you treat
him like that?
We just couldn't handle him
being fully paralyzed.
We didn't know what else to do.
But you're right.
We got to get him out of there.
You most certainly do.
All right, how about
that back rub now?
What are you, nuts?
What the hell do you want?
Oh, hello, sir.
I'm afraid there's
been a mistake.
I believe you found our dog,
and we need to take him home.
No way!
Get lost, kid.
He's my dog now.
Well, we figured
you'd say no to us,
but not to Vice President
Joe Biden!
Oh, my God!
Mr. Vice President!
First, I want
to thank you, Vic,
for shooting the guy
we said was Osama bin Laden.
Second, give these kids
their dog back.
Of course, sir,
I'm so sorry!
Here, take him!
Thank you.
You're a great American.
Thanks, Mr. Biden!
No problem.
Hey, you guys watch Veep?
No.
Yeah, it's all fake.
Yeah, we said no.
Hi, uh, we're here
to pick up Joe Swanson.
Are you from the news?
You have to tell us
if you're from the news.
No, we're his friends.
What are you guys
doing here?
We came to bring
you home, Joe.
We're all really sorry
we abandoned you.
Yeah, we just kind of got
overwhelmed and all freaked out.
But we're your
friends, Joe.
And we'll always be there
for you no matter what.
Thanks, guys.
I'd say let's get my stuff,
but it's all been stolen.
That's okay.
Come on, let's go home.
Sorry, no one
gets out of here
without a release
from their doctor.
All right, we'll just
call him right now.
What's that ringing?
Joe, that ringing--
it's coming from your back!
It is?
Holy crap!
Dr. Hartman must have
dropped his phone in Joe
when he was looking
at his spine!
Oh, thank God.
I've been hearing
that ringing all week.
I just thought
I was losing my mind
from lunatics
screaming in my face.
Your mother's a whore!
I told you that
in confidence, Gary.
Ah, it's so great
to have you back, Joe.
You seem good as new.
Yeah, it turns out Dr.
Hartman's cell phone
was pressing on
my spinal cord,
and that's what was causing
my total paralysis.
Yeah, sorry we dropped
the ball for a while,
which is the way we agreed we'd
describe what we did to you,
which hopefully
makes it seem less heinous.
It's all right, guys.
I'm just glad to be
back on my feet.
Well, you know
what I mean.
I never saw much
of Joe after that.
And while he's been gone
for many years,
I've never forgotten his face
or his laughter.
Come on, are we
going to the beach?
We've been waiting forever.
Yeah, be right there,
champ.
He said that the first
two times we asked.
I know, he spaces out
when he's at the computer.
These aren't my kids.
And also, this isn't
play wrestling.
We're actually fighting.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru